<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Keywords on A Dog walks into a Noise Concert</title>
    <link>http://example.org/keywords/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Keywords on A Dog walks into a Noise Concert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 14:37:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/keywords/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DJ Screw</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/dj-screw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 14:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/dj-screw/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common Sense</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/common-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/common-sense/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/computer/</guid>
      <description>Each time I start up my laptop it greets me with this message:
error: ../../grub-core/commands/search.c:315:no such device: /EFI/custom/apple_set_os.efi. error: ../../grub-core/fs/fshelp.c:257:file ‘/EFI/custom/apple_set_os.efi’ not found. error: ../../grub-core/commands/boot.c:196:you need to load the kernel first.
A hacker is also a vandal1
What’s the Use, Sara Ahmed (2019), p.225&amp;#160;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/event/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/event/</guid>
      <description>If you are playing with your band and you play a wrong note, don&amp;rsquo;t freeze but play on. Act as if nothing happened. The listener will think that the note is part of the arrangement, they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t even notice and will keep dancing to the beat. When on the other hand you, or worse, the whole band stops playing, the listener will notice. They will wonder what happened. The train has stopped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knight</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/knight/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/knight/</guid>
      <description>My favourite chess piece is the knight. In Dutch we call it &amp;lsquo;het paard&amp;rsquo; (the horse). Like the rook, the knight is not human. The rook, as an inanimate object, is static. It can only move up or down, left or right. The knight as an animal, is not fixed to one colour, row, or column. It jumps around and over other pieces. First two squares in one direction, then one square to the left or right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Language</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/language/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/language/</guid>
      <description>I have always have had a troubled relationship with language. When I was younger I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to speak language at all. Instead, I pointed. *&amp;ldquo;it is that,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;it is not that.&amp;rdquo;1 My fingers were like the sharp points of a ‌fork. Piercing all the things I wanted to eat. to eat or to speak[^ Ibid., p.23] Now that I did develop the ability to speak, there is still more food going in than words coming out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manifest</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/manifest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/manifest/</guid>
      <description>These are the words that I manifest, I [manifest.[^ Manifest - Gang Starr]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noise</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/noise/</guid>
      <description>What is the fun of attending a noise concert where the sound technician has an off day and where you feel your bones vibrate along with the towering speakers? A million watts are shaking the room.[^ Solid Wall of Sound - A Tribe Called Quest] The noise fills you up. There is no room left for thoughts. All of your parts, your organs, your feet, your shoulders, your eyes, your brain, they stopped colliding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pawn</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/pawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/pawn/</guid>
      <description>supernumary object</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pervert</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/pervert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/pervert/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/radio/</guid>
      <description>The crackling fire of the untuned noise helps me concentrate. It became a condition to write, to be drowned in noise. To drown the noise inside with noise from outside. I emptied a wall. The corner of my room became an empty space, to be filled with noise. The noise hides in between the natural numbers. Between Sky Radio and Amor FM, at around 102.0 MHz is where I can concentrate, it is where the train stops because of a defect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silence</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/silence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/silence/</guid>
      <description>Silence
Stap uit je comfortzone, ik heb geen comfortzone[^ Mandola - Roosbeef (2023)]
There is nothing to say about nothing, so I will try to write about silence. If you say something, it passes through your lips; so, if you say &amp;ldquo;chariot&amp;rdquo;, a chariot passes through your lips.[^ Gilles Deleuze, The Logic of Sense (1969), p.22] Initialy it seems comfortable to remain in silence. A turn away. Sitting, waiting, watching, hoping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stalemate</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/stalemate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/stalemate/</guid>
      <description>They stand at a stay; Like a Stale at Chesse, where is no Mate, but yet the game cannot Stirre[^ Bacon, Essayes (1625) via David Hooper, Kenneth Whyld, The Oxford Companion to Chess (1992)]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAMO</title>
      <link>http://example.org/keywords/tamo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/keywords/tamo/</guid>
      <description>When my mother was twenty-two years old, she and her brother discovered that their father had disappeared. He left the Netherlands and headed towards the south of France. He settled in a small village, Roquebrune-Cap-Martin, and started his romantic artist existence. His artist name was TAMO. We visited him once a year at least. Those visits, seeing the good life and the turquoise sea, always impressed me and I looked up to him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
